{
    "subject": "Ali_Selim",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Sweet_Land",
    "human_readable": "Ali Selim directed Sweet Land.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.727028489112854,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Ali Selim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7106199860572815,
            "question": "Who directed the film Sweet Land?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6655011177062988,
            "question": "Is Ali Selim a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6154400706291199,
            "question": "Has Ali Selim directed any other films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35033535957336426,
            "question": "Are there any actors known for their roles in Sweet Land?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30056366324424744,
            "question": "What year was Sweet Land released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.289695680141449,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of Sweet Land?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2293655425310135,
            "question": "Where can I watch Sweet Land?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20617565512657166,
            "question": "What genre is Sweet Land likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17939803004264832,
            "question": "What awards has Sweet Land won?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ali Selim directed Sweet Land.",
            "html": "yago_12096_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Sweet Land likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_12096_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I watch Sweet Land?",
            "html": "yago_12096_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the plot of Sweet Land?",
            "html": "yago_12096_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12096_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12096_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12096_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12096_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12096_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12096_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12096_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12096_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12096_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12096_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Ali Selim is the director of \"Sweet Land,\" which supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}